welcome back so answer interest having
欢迎回来，所以回答有兴趣
people in this room the in the earlier
这个房间里的人
two sessions
两节
okay so I'm guessing that's about half
好吧，我猜大概是一半
of everyone so for the half of everyone
每个人的一半
who's already in here you either already
谁已经在这里你要么已经
know this before you came to the
在您来之前知道这一点
conference or you've heard a lot of the
会议，或者您已经听到很多
same material so I'm going to apologize
相同的材料，我要道歉
I've been frantically trying to work out
我一直在疯狂地努力锻炼
how to say this you know say things in a
这个怎么说你知道吗
different and fresh way and I also have
不同和新鲜的方式，我也有
a lot of code demos which I was
我当时的很多代码演示
rewriting this morning during Emily's
在艾米丽（Emily）的今天早上重写
talk so fingers crossed everything will
说话，让手指越过一切
work so my name is ice nottingham i work
工作，所以我叫冰诺丁汉，我工作
for IBM i've worked for IBM for too long
我为IBM工作了太长时间了
17 years I'm since 2001 and I've worked
从2001年开始我已经工作了17年
on the application server but I'm not
在应用程序服务器上，但我不是
going to talk about the application
将要讨论的应用程序
server massively today because it's
今天大量服务器，因为它
mostly about micro profile so before I
主要是关于微轮廓，所以在我之前
go in and start talking about the
进入并开始谈论
microphone APRs I want to kind of
我想要的麦克风APR
reflect slightly on the kind of the last
稍微反思一下过去的那种
few years and how we have got to the
几年，以及我们如何到达
point where we are really needing new
指出我们真正需要新的地方
api's because I think some of the comms
api是因为我认为一些通讯
context of really helps to understand
的上下文确实有助于理解
why some things are the way they are and
为什么有些事情是这样的？
why they're important rather than just
为什么它们很重要而不是仅仅
assuming it is because everyone says it
假设是因为每个人都说
is and at least from my perspective this
是，至少从我看来
all started with agile when I first
我刚开始时都是从敏捷开始的
joined IBM and when I was at university
加入IBM并在我上大学的时候
everyone talked about waterfall as being
每个人都说瀑布是
kind of a development model that was
一种开发模型
still considered to be in vogue and of
仍被认为是时尚和
course these days if you came out of
当然这些天，如果你出来
university and you said waterfall is the
大学，你说瀑布是
way to develop software you would
开发软件的方式
probably be laughed out of the room in
可能在房间外面被笑了
most most companies and the reason why
大多数公司及其原因
people were wanted to adopt agile was to
人们想要采用敏捷是为了
get kind of faster delivery cycles but
获得更快的交付周期，但
also to kind of push decision-making
也要推动决策
down and to break up kind of development
下来，打破那种发展
teams they could be developing and
他们可能正在发展的团队
delivering more on their own but it was
自己提供更多，但这是
really concerned originally with how do
最初真正关心的是如何做
you develop and deliver code and then
您开发并交付代码，然后
DevOps came along and dev what DevOps
DevOps出现并开发了什么DevOps
said was you know we understand how to
说是你知道我们知道如何
do code but configure
做代码，但配置
machines is really hard and you know if
机器真的很难，你知道
emissions suddenly stops working
排放突然停止工作
properly it's really hard to get
正确地很难得到
something new set up the same way as it
一些新的设置方法
was before well why don't we just script
之前我们为什么不只是编写脚本
it all and write code and then you know
全部编写代码，然后您就会知道
infrastructure as code came into being
代码产生的基础架构
and that got that whole thing was idea
那整个事情就是主意
was let's integrate that into the
让我们将其整合到
development teams the development team
开发团队开发团队
deliver both the code and some in
提供代码和一些
scripts which would allow their machines
允许他们的机器运行的脚本
that the applications run on to be set
运行应用程序进行设置
up and provisioned and reproducibly and
设置和可复制
you know the first time we were being
你知道我们是第一次
told about DevOps in and the need to do
讲述了有关DevOps的内容以及需要做的事情
DevOps in IBM you know we were still in
IBM中的DevOps，您知道我们还在
a world of you know you'd go and ask for
你的世界知道你会去寻求
a virtual machine you set up a virtual
建立虚拟机的虚拟机
machine and the virtual machine would
机和虚拟机将
exist and live there for you know a year
存在并生活在那里，你知道一年
two years maybe and then what cloud did
也许两年，然后云做了什么
is it came along and brought along the
它来了吗？
idea but you know these things and these
想法，但是你知道这些东西
machines you get them for a relatively
机器，你得到他们相对
short period of time you set them up you
在很短的时间内设置好您
run them and you throw them away so for
运行它们，然后将它们丢弃
example within the team I work in one of
我在以下团队之一工作的例子
the advantages it gave us was instead of
它给我们带来的好处不是
having to constantly worry about making
不得不不断担心制作
sure the operating systems or software
确保操作系统或软件
always patched you just throw it away
总是打补丁，你只是把它扔掉
and reprovision something from scratch
并从头开始重新配置
so you would get the base image to be
这样您就可以得到基本图像
updated with all the fixes and then
更新了所有修复程序，然后
you're very provisional of the machines
你是非常临时的机器
and that gets integrated with your
并与您的
DevOps flow and your agile development
DevOps流程和您的敏捷开发
flow and that's what leads to essential
流动，这就是必不可少的
the essential desire to go with micro
微型的基本愿望
services because when you have lots and
服务，因为当你有很多
lots of teams all trying to work
很多团队都在努力工作
independently I'm trying to coordinate
我正在独立尝试
and get all of those application code to
并获取所有这些应用程序代码
run in a single JVM and a single
在单个JVM和单个JVM中运行
application server requires a lot of
应用服务器需要很多
coordination which slows down the
协调会减慢
delivery cycle so as fast as you can go
交货周期尽可能快
with agile and DevOps and the cloud
与敏捷，DevOps和云
provisioning you also need to be able to
供应您还需要能够
get the teams to be able to work more
让团队能够更多地工作
independently of each other and that's
彼此独立，那是
kind of where micro services come from
微服务的来源
the problem with the with that is the
的问题是
general approaches use kind of REST API
通用方法使用一种REST API
so messaging API so to get the
这样的消息传递API，以便获得
interaction between the services working
服务工作之间的交互
which brings you into the whole world of
带您进入整个世界
distributed programming
分布式编程
and you get a whole load of additional
你会得到额外的负担
problems that you didn't have to worry
您不必担心的问题
about with the old ways of developing
关于旧的发展方式
and delivering applications and you know
和交付应用程序，您知道
so when you look at the what you want
所以当你看着你想要的
from your kind of cloud native and your
来自您自己的云原生和
cloud environments you want api's that
您想要api的云环境
support distributed computing you want
支持您想要的分布式计算
something that starts up and shuts down
开始和关闭的东西
very quickly especially if you're trying
非常快，特别是如果您正在尝试
to do scale up you want to scale up
做放大你想放大
because your workload is increasing you
因为你的工作量增加了你
don't have to wait you know twenty-five
不必等待，您知道二十五岁
minutes or thirty minutes to be able to
分钟或三十分钟就可以
cope with a sudden burst of new requests
应付突然出现的新要求
you want it to be a small footprint
您希望它的占地面积很小
because quite often you're getting
因为很多时候你会得到
charged based on the memory footprint or
根据内存占用量或
the CPU footprint or the disk footprint
CPU占用空间或磁盘占用空间
in these environments you're something
在这些环境中，您就是
that's very small and you want to have
那很小，你想拥有
development production parity you want
您想要的开发生产平价
to externalize configurations you want
外部化您想要的配置
it to be very easy for you your
对你来说很容易
developer to deliver something and then
开发人员交付一些东西，然后
that gets deployed into the multiple
被部署到多个
different deployment environments you
您不同的部署环境
might have with different configurations
可能具有不同的配置
so your developer doesn't have access to
因此您的开发人员无权访问
production databases especially in GDP
生产数据库，特别是GDP
our world you don't want your developers
我们的世界，你不想要你的开发商
to have access to production databases
可以访问生产数据库
and increasingly people want things to
越来越多的人想要事物
be container are easily containerized
被容器容易地集装箱化
because docker is kind of fast becoming
因为码头工人正在迅速成为
the go-to way of getting your
获取您的首选方法
applications deployed in Klauss so Java
应用程序部署在Klauss中，因此Java
EE or as it is now now becoming Jakarta
EE或现在正成为雅加达
EE has existed for quite a while but
EE已经存在了一段时间，但
over its history what's happened the few
在其历史上发生了什么事
things have happened over at history one
历史已经发生了一件事情
is it's got a lot of capabilities being
它有很多功能吗
put into it and some of those things
放入其中以及其中一些东西
aren't in vogue anymore if you're
如果您已经不再流行
writing micro services you're almost
编写微服务，您差不多
certainly not using a IOP as the
当然不使用IOP作为
communication layer between your micro
您的微电脑之间的通讯层
services it's much more likely that
服务更有可能
you're using something that is
您正在使用的是
lightweight messaging like Kafka or
轻量级消息传递，例如Kafka或
you're using rest the other problem that
您正在使用其余的另一个问题
this this stack is other than you've got
这个堆栈不是你所拥有的
an awful lot of technology most people
大多数人都有很多技术
aren't using which led to Java
没有使用导致Java
integrally having a reputation of being
具有整体声誉的人
bloated is the release cycles for java
Java的发布周期肿
re' have been slow
re'已经很慢
down at the same time as the industry
与行业同时下跌
has been trying to speed up so it was
一直试图加快速度，所以
you know was identified as a problem a
你知道被确定为问题
few years ago and people from Red Hat
几年前，来自Red Hat的人们
and Tommy tribe and IBM and a few other
还有汤米部落和IBM等
people were at a conference and they
人们在开会，他们
said we need to do something about this
说我们需要为此做些事情
and that is the genesis of the micro
这就是微观的起源
profile project and you know the put
个人资料项目，您知道投放
these problems that exist around it
这些周围存在的问题
looking big and fat you know almost
看起来又大又胖你几乎知道
everyone in the industry is trying to
行业中的每个人都在尝试
deal with this you know how can we
处理这个，你知道我们怎么能
deliver the java re' capabilities
提供Java re功能
without everyone having to take
无需每个人都采取
everything so with liberty which is the
一切都是自由的
runtime that i work on in IBM we took an
我在IBM工作的运行时我们花了一个
approach that we were decompose the java
我们分解Java的方法
re' specifications into things called
规格被称为
features and you could configure a mix
功能，您可以配置混合
and match the features you want so if
并匹配您想要的功能，如果
you want to have jax-rs and you want to
你想拥有jax-rs并且你想要
do open api you can get those two things
打开api可以得到这两件事
but you don't have to take the EJB
但您不必采用EJB
container the web services stack and so
容器Web服务堆栈等
on and in fact we're not the only people
事实上，我们并不是唯一的人
who are thinking along these lines
谁在按照这些思路思考
because thorn tail which is the new name
因为刺尾是新名字
for wild flow swarm essentially has the
对于野生流群基本上具有
same model you can opt into the parts of
您可以选择采用相同的模型
the runtime you need the advantage of
运行时，您需要以下优势
this is it means that your runtimes get
这意味着您的运行时
smaller they start faster and they they
较小的它们开始更快，他们
use less memory for the application
为应用程序使用更少的内存
needs you have so all of that thing
需要你拥有所有这些东西
about java re' being kind of big and
关于Java re'有点大而
heavy weight is kind of no longer true
沉重的重量不再是真的
unless you're still using an application
除非您仍在使用应用程序
server from like 10-15 years ago
大约10到15年前的服务器
so Eclipse micro profile is I took the
所以我用Eclipse的微配置文件
Eclipse project we started I think it
我认为我们开始的Eclipse项目
was a year and a half maybe two years
一年半也许两年
ago now and it's actually got quite a
现在以前，它实际上已经
lot of companies who are involved and
很多参与其中的公司
interested in it being successful
对它成功感兴趣
most recently like Bend and Microsoft
最近像Bend和Microsoft
during the joint party which is really
在联合聚会中
interesting and useful some of that was
有趣和有用的一些是
driven I think partly by interest in in
我认为部分原因是对
and the movement of Java EE to eclipse
以及Java EE的日蚀
but what we're trying to do at micro
但是我们在微电子上要做的是
profile is to accelerate the delivery of
简介是为了加快交付
new programming models that build on
建立在新的编程模型之上
kind of Java EE and originally when java
种Java EE，最初是Java
re' was still in the JCP we thought
re'仍在我们认为的JCP中
we'll develop these in micro file and
我们将在微型文件中开发这些文件，
they're more standardized not sure
他们更标准化不确定
exactly what's going to go on with the
到底会发生什么
relationship moving forward but it's
关系向前发展，但这是
it'll it'll work we'll make it work
它会工作，我们会使其工作
because most of these cups are involved
因为这些杯子大多数都涉及
in Jakarta EE as well so as I said if
就像我说的那样，在雅加达EE中
you're doing micro services I'm gonna
你在做微服务，我要
move into demos you're probably using
进入您可能正在使用的演示
REST API s and we started talking about
REST API，我们开始谈论
the base of micro profile we said let's
我们说过的微观概况的基础
just start with rest we need to start
只是从休息开始，我们需要开始
somewhere and regionally defined CDI
某个地区和地区定义的CDI
JSONP and jax-rs as the core kind of
JSONP和jax-rs是核心
rest components and much more recently
其余组件以及最近的组件
we've added a template-based rest
我们添加了基于模板的休息
clients and there's I think I never
客户，我想我从来没有
taught that might may be another talk on
教导可能是另一回事
that No okay so I'm going to do so I'm
那不行，所以我要去做，我是
going to do a quick demo of all of these
将对所有这些进行快速演示
and
和
so I'm in my demo I have probably the
所以我在演示中可能有
most over-engineered bit of Java code
最过度设计的Java代码
I've ever had the misfortune of writing
我曾经有过写作的不幸
and I write Java code which means almost
我写的Java代码几乎
all of the Java code I write is over
我写的所有Java代码都结束了
engineered in some way I have a service
以某种方式设计的我可以提供服务
called service C which returns system
称为服务C，它返回系统
properties and I have a service a which
属性，我有一个服务
essentially just returns the results
本质上只是返回结果
from service C and the reason for this
来自服务C的原因
is service a can call service C and
是服务，可以致电服务C，
basically tell service C to simulate
基本上告诉服务C模拟
several bad conditions so I can ask
几个恶劣的条件，所以我可以问
service C to do something differently
服务C做一些不同的事情
based on the input parameters to
根据输入参数
demonstrate some of them microphone
演示一些麦克风
capabilities so I'm going to let's go
功能，所以我要走了
and find code so okay
并找到代码就可以了
I've seen people can read this so
我已经看到人们可以阅读这篇文章
basically this is my service C code and
基本上这是我的服务C代码，
I have a I have a method and basically
我有一个方法，基本上
what it does is it takes property you
它所做的是它带给您财产
give it a mode and a property name and
给它一个模式和一个属性名，
it basically live what this beam here
它基本上住在这里
does I'll show you in a second but it
我会告诉你一秒钟吗
basically looks at the mode and based on
基本上看模式，并根据
the mode it does some different behavior
该模式执行一些不同的行为
so if you say you want it to be slow it
所以如果你说你希望它慢一点
adds asleep so it'll take at least two
增加睡眠，因此至少需要两个
seconds to respond so it simulates about
秒响应，因此模拟
a service that's having some kind of
具有某种意义的服务
issue or it returns a failure or it
问题或返回失败或
returns a failure sometimes and inside
有时会在内部返回失败
of the might be in code it's just doing
可能在代码中只是在做
system get property which is kind of why
系统获取属性，这就是为什么
I say it's the most engineered code I've
我说这是我做过的最精心设计的代码
ever written and in service a I have a
曾经写过并且在服役中，我有一个
REST API which basically is calling a
REST API基本上是在调用
helper and the helper in this case is
助手和助手在这种情况下是
just apparently not compiling I've been
只是显然不编译我去过
having problems with the s code
s代码有问题
and it calls their equals the client
它称其等于客户
interface using get prop with none and
使用get prop的界面，并且没有和
if you look here what's what I'm doing
如果你看这里我在做什么
is I'm having objected the rest client
我反对其他客户吗
and if I look at the rest client it's
如果我看看其余的客户
using the template based approach so you
使用基于模板的方法
annotate it with jax-rs annotations and
用jax-rs注释对其进行注释，然后
you say it's a registering arrest it's
你说这是一个登记逮捕
fine and then on the method I've say I
很好，然后在方法上我说我
when someone calls this method I want to
当有人调用此方法时，我想
do a get to this path it produces
去做这条路
application Jason and I specify this
应用程序Jason和我指定了这个
would be go through as a query parameter
将作为查询参数
and
和
this is a path parameter so when you
这是一个路径参数，所以当您
call the I've not had to implement the
称我不必实施
interface of them to write their new
他们编写新界面的界面
jax-rs client code I just had to
我只需要的jax-rs客户代码
annotate the interface I can then get it
给接口加注释，然后就可以得到它
injected and
注入并
I am really hoping that when I run
我真的很希望当我跑步时
through this it works and the compiler
通过它可以工作并且编译器
isn't something edgy to worry about
不必担心前卫
okay apparently I'm not being lucky this
好吧，显然我不是很幸运
did work before I came in
在我进来之前做过工作
I do package let's see if my maven
我做包装让我们看看我的行家
compiles
编译
yeah
是的
okay so that's all compiled so hopefully
好的，所以希望所有这些都可以编译
yeah okay so now all I'm doing you're
是的，好吧，现在我正在做的是
notif if i zoom in so you'll notice here
如果我放大，您会在这里注意到
I'm not doing anything special
我没什么特别的
so I'm asking for service name and it's
所以我要索取服务名称，
tellin you it's service C but if you
告诉你这是服务C，但是如果你
look in the URL path here it says its
看URL路径在这里说
I'm calling service a rather than
我称服务不是
service C so this is just a diamond what
服务C，所以这只是钻石而已
I'm doing is I have a demo later where
我正在做的是稍后再演示
this will turn a different value but
这将变成一个不同的值，但是
this is just showing I'm kind of just
这只是表明我有点
proc seeing it through okay
proc看到一切顺利
so if that's just the very basics of how
所以如果这仅仅是如何
the sample is working micro profile also
样品也在起作用
is trying to look at how you man how you
试图看看你如何对待你
providing a place to let you manage
提供一个让您管理的地方
services when you have a large number of
当您有大量的服务时
them I say hundreds here but for some
他们我在这里说数百
some applications 10 might be a large
一些应用程序10可能很大
number so we've added a ps4 health check
数字，所以我们添加了PS4健康检查
open API and metrics
开放的API和指标
and I have 15 minutes left and if I go
还有15分钟，如果我走
back I'm going to show the health check
返回我要出示健康检查
which is it so I've written a I've got
是的，所以我写了一个
my health endpoint and I can hit this
我的健康终点，我可以做到这一点
and refresh it and what the code is
并刷新它，代码是什么
doing is what the code does is it's
代码是做什么的
making
制造
okay that's better so what the code here
好的，那更好，这里的代码
we're doing is I'm getting the your L to
我们正在做的是让您的L
service C injected using config I'm
服务C使用配置注入我
creating the jax-rs clients not the same
创建jax-rs客户端不一样
one I used before I'm now using the code
我现在使用代码之前使用过的一种
I would have written otherwise and then
我本来会写，然后
when I make their get request and I look
当我向他们提出要求时，我看起来
for status of 200 and they return false
状态为200且它们返回false
so if I were to go and shut down the
所以如果我要去关闭
service C which I can do this is
我可以做到的服务C是
missionary to the right one down yep so
传教士右边是这样
if I shut down service C and go back and
如果我关闭服务C并返回
now refresh you'll see it switched down
现在刷新，您将看到它已关闭
so I wouldn't recommend kind of writing
所以我不推荐那种写作
health checks quite in this way because
通过这种方式进行健康检查，因为
you should write your code to be
你应该写你的代码是
resilient to service e going down and be
有弹性地应对服务下降
able to cope but this is a simple way of
能够应付，但这是一种简单的方法
demonstrating that your health care can
证明您的医疗保健可以
write some code and do some logic to
编写一些代码并做一些逻辑
work out whether it's up and what you
弄清楚它是否启动以及您正在做什么
might do inside of the health check is
健康检查里面可能做的是
do things like make sure if you're
做类似的事情来确保你是否
calling your own database make sure in
调用自己的数据库，确保输入
the database is up you might be looking
数据库启动，您可能正在寻找
at you might be starting up so you're
在你可能正在启动，所以你
making sure any internal caches and you
确保任何内部缓存和您
indicate that you're down until you're
表示你沮丧，直到你
in total caches are built up and that
总缓存已建立，并且
means that when you're running in a
表示当您在
cloud environment you can make sure that
云环境中，您可以确保
the front end Reuter isn't routing
前端路透社没有路由
traffic to you so if you're in a
吸引您，所以如果您在
kubernetes environment it can check this
kubernetes环境可以检查一下
health point and until this returns up
健康点，直到恢复
it weren't route traffic to it so I'm
它没有路由流量，所以我
just going to bring that up another
只是要提出另一个
thing that we did is we we've we've got
我们所做的是，我们拥有
here is you we can generate open API
这是您我们可以生成开放API
documents are based on the jax-rs
文档基于jax-rs
annotations you can also provide an open
注释也可以提供一个开放的
API documentation for your REST API and
REST API和
you can annotate additional data into
您可以将其他数据注释为
your your jax-rs and the nice thing
您的jax-rs和美好的事物
about that is you can then get a user
关于那是你可以然后得到一个用户
interface you can kind of use this this
界面，您可以使用此
open API browsing application and start
打开API浏览应用程序并启动
interacting with it without with the
与之互动而不与
with the API so if I want to say I want
使用API​​，所以如果我想说我想要
to do a get it tells me that there's a
做它告诉我，有一个
mode query string and a prop query
模式查询字符串和属性查询
string and I can try it out and I'm not
字符串，我可以尝试一下，但我不是
going to indicate what a mode is but I'm
会指出什么是模式，但是我
going to say I want a property so I'm
会说我想要房产所以我
going to say job at home and then if I
要说在家工作，如果我
click execute the load it'll tell me the
点击执行加载，它会告诉我
Java home of my Java is installed down
我的Java的Java主页已安装
and apparently I'm using Java 9 which I
显然我正在使用Java 9
didn't intend to do so fingers crossed
不想这样做
everything works when he seen Java 9
当他看到Java 9时一切正常
rather than one point a which is and the
而不是一个点是和
other thing that we added if I go
如果我去的话，我们添加的其他内容
yeah another thing we added is metrics
是的，我们添加的另一件事是指标
so one of the things that Joffrey didn't
所以乔佛里没有的一件事
really have was a way for applications
确实是一种应用程序
to contribute metrics most application
为大多数应用贡献指标
servers define some metrics there were
服务器定义了一些指标
some specifications defined mbeans for
一些规范定义了用于
metrics but there wasn't any way from
指标，但没有任何办法
applications abies of the metrics that
应用程序的指标
are important to my application as
对我的应用程序很重要，因为
opposed to these are the metrics that
与这些相对的是
the application server thinks you might
应用程序服务器认为您可能
be interested in so what what we did in
有兴趣，所以我们在做什么
micro for metrics is we defined some
微型指标，我们定义了一些
annotations and and some api's for
注释和一些api
building up your own application related
建立自己的应用程序相关
things so for example on this method
事情，例如这种方法
which is in service C I have an at time
CI正在使用哪个
to annotation and act count it not at
注释并采取行动而不是在
time does is it says time how long the
时间是不是说时间多久了
method execute form and you can then get
方法执行表格，然后您可以获取
this information fed into something like
这些信息输入到类似
Prometheus and you as which is a
普罗米修斯和你一样
monitoring tool and your monitoring tool
监视工具和您的监视工具
can then do things like tell you when
然后可以做一些事情，比如告诉你什么时候
your method invocation is starting to
您的方法调用开始
slow down and that might be an
放慢脚步，那可能是
indication that there's a problem and
表示有问题，
you need to take creative action and you
您需要采取创造性的行动，您
can apply it to the methods which you
可以将其应用于您所使用的方法
think are important rather than it being
认为重要而不是重要
say the servlet methods or the jax-rs
说servlet方法或jax-rs
methods so any CDI Bean can have this if
方法，因此任何CDI Bean都可以拥有
you know there's a CDI Bean that's
你知道有一个CDI Bean
expensive or is likely to hit these kind
昂贵或可能击中此类
of problems you can put the annotation
有问题可以放注释
around exactly the code that you're
完全围绕您的代码
interested in and I've also used that
感兴趣，我也用过
counted which basically counts the
算，这基本上算
number of times something is executed so
执行某件事的次数，因此
they go to the Prometheus user interface
他们进入Prometheus用户界面
and I'm just going to refresh this
我只是要刷新一下
you'll see there's a kind of this beena
你会发现这里有一种bea
graph of where i've been testing it and
我一直在测试的图形
then because i refreshed it does not
然后因为我刷新了
there's been only one invocation which
只有一个调用
hopefully you can read there and if i go
希望你可以在那里阅读，如果我去
back and i refresh let me refresh
返回，我刷新让我刷新
service c directly it should
直接服务c
should
应该
it shouldn't yeah you can just about see
不应该，你可以看看
it subject to two so there's been
它受两个约束，所以有
another invocation so when I do an
另一个调用，所以当我做一个
invocation it gets presented here
调用在此处显示
directly
直
okay so the next thing I want that so
好吧，接下来我想这样
being able to monitor isn't necessarily
能够监控不一定
enough you also want to be able to we
足够您还希望我们能够
also needed thought we need to provide
还需要我们需要提供的思想
some additional api's to the programming
编程的一些其他API
model to deal with these distributed
处理这些分布式模型
systems so I've shown you a little bit
系统，所以我向您展示了一些
of config I haven't I'm not going to
的配置，我没有，我不会
show JWT because I don't have time but I
向JWT展示，因为我没有时间，但我
have got a couple of examples of using
有一些使用示例
for tolerance and you've seen some of
为了宽容，你已经看到了一些
them already so I may be going over some
他们已经，所以我可能要去一些
new ground but if I go back this is the
新领域，但如果我回去，这就是
bit that I'm a little bit nervous about
有点让我有点紧张
because I've read it at all this morning
因为我今天早上都看过
so in the service not this one so in
所以在服务中不是这样的
service a rest I was I've got this fetch
服务休息我是我已经得到了
service prop helper and this fetch
服务道具助手和此获取
service opera if I show it to you it
服务歌剧，如果我给你看
just is calling client got that from get
只是打电话给客户从得到
prop with none as the mode so what I
没有模式作为道具，所以我
want to do is I want to simulate an
想做的是我想模拟一个
error condition so what I'm going to do
错误情况，所以我要做什么
is I'm going to tell the downstream
我要告诉下游
service
服务
that I want it
我想要
that's wait that's right one of the
等待，那是正确的之一
qualifiers are compiled
限定词被编译
now
现在
okay great that's fixed that on so so I
好吧，那已经固定了，所以我
have this this beam here which basically
这里有这个光束，基本上
is exactly the same as the vanilla one
与香草香草完全一样
except I've said some times and
除了我说过几次
whatsoever C will do when I say
当我说C时会做什么
sometimes this it will fail everything
有时这会使一切失败
every other time and then all I need to
每隔一段时间，然后我需要
do in my rest service is tell it to
在我的休息服务中要做的就是告诉
inject the at sometimes version of the
注入有时的
beam instead so now if I go back to here
相反，所以现在如果我回到这里
I go refresh it says over 500 I can't
我去刷新它说超过500我不能
resolve and if i refresh again it works
解决，如果我再次刷新它可以工作
and if I were to look at prometheus if i
如果我要看普罗米修斯，如果我
refresh the graph you'll actually notice
刷新您实际上会注意到的图形
up here it's got four because I'm
在这里有四个，因为我
actually simulating a failure as opposed
实际上是模拟失败
to the so it's got into the target being
到目标就可以了
but you know nobody wants you know if
但是你知道没有人想要你知道
you're the owner of service air you
您是Air Air的所有者
don't want to be called out when service
不想在服务时被召唤
C starts spitting spurious arrows at you
C开始向您吐出虚假箭头
so what you can do in this case is you
所以在这种情况下你可以做的是
can use the retry you can use the retry
可以使用重试可以使用重试
annotation so if I add that retry so
注解，所以如果我添加该重试
this method what it'll do is it will ask
这种方法将要问的是
the CDI interceptor blue be configured
CDI拦截器蓝色被配置
so if it fails it will automatically do
因此，如果失败，它将自动执行
a retry and it's configurable how many
重试，并且可以配置多少
we tries what time units to put between
我们尝试放置什么时间单位
but I'm just adding an a tree tree
但我只是添加一棵树
annotation for the simple case here and
这里的简单案例的注释和
now if i refresh it takes a little bit
现在，如果我刷新需要一点时间
longer but it's responding each time and
更长，但每次都响应
again if I go to the Prometheus you'll
再一次，如果我去普罗米修斯，你会
see it's gone up and it's at eight at
看到它上升了，现在是八点
the moment if I go back and refresh
我回去刷新的那一刻
again and I come back and refresh here
再次，我回到这里刷新
it should have gone up to ten and it has
它应该上升到十，它已经
so that's how you can see it's doing two
这样便可以看到它正在做两个
requests because Prometheus is telling
请求，因为普罗米修斯在告诉
us there have been two requests just by
我们只有两个请求
the fact I only did a single refresh
我只刷新了一个事实
that time
那时
so that's how to do that's how you can
所以这就是这样做的方法
use retry another thing you might want
使用重试您可能想要的另一件事
to do is you might have the service
要做的是您可能有服务
which is getting into trouble it's
麻烦了
slowing down maybe there's too much load
放慢脚步，也许负载太大
on it so each request is taking longer
在它上面，所以每个请求花费更长的时间
so I'm going to inject a different
所以我要注入一个不同的
different version which
不同版本
is this slow it's the slow version and
这是慢版本吗？
if I look at the note I'm out helper
如果我看一下便条，我就是帮手
which is what I get injected when I say
这就是我说的话
slow I've I'm pushing a mode in of slow
我已经将慢速模式推入
and what slow tells to ever sees you is
慢速告诉你的就是
just to wait for two seconds so if I go
只是等待两秒钟，所以如果我走
back and I I go and request it now it's
回来，我去要求它，现在是
gonna take a little bit of time and this
要花一点时间，这
is this is kind of dull to watch but
这有点沉闷吗
you'll notice it's taking a bit longer
您会发现它花了更长的时间
to respond so that's not great for me
回应，所以这对我来说不是很好
because I've now missed mice SLA and I'm
因为我现在想念老鼠SLA而我
getting phone calls from my clients
接到客户的电话
telling me why you slowing me down
告诉我为什么你放慢我的速度
rather than service C having to be
而不是服务C必须是
dragged out of bed at 2:00 a.m. in the
在凌晨2:00在床上下床
morning so in this case what I'm going
早上，在这种情况下，我要去的是
to do is I'm get out the timeout
要做的就是我超时了
annotation and I'm going to tell it I
注释，我要告诉我
want it to timeout after five hundred
要五百分钟后超时
milliseconds so if I go back now and i
毫秒，所以如果我现在回去
refresh it's going to do about five
刷新大约要执行五次
hundred seconds and then I'm get a nasty
一百秒，然后我就讨厌了
horrible error so now my client knows
可怕的错误，所以现在我的客户知道
that there was a timeout condition which
有一个超时条件
is really great
真的很棒
but I'm still being called out of bed so
但我仍然被叫起床
I've met my time SLA but I haven't met
我已经满足了我的时间SLA，但还没有满足
my API agreement because I'm still
我的API协议，因为我仍然
returning failure so I'm still gonna get
返回失败，所以我仍然会得到
pulled out better early in the morning
清晨拉出更好
so in this case to deal with this what
所以在这种情况下要处理什么
I'm going to do is I'm going to find a
我要做的就是找到一个
fallback and you can just add an
后备，您可以添加一个
annotation or fallback and I'm going to
注释或后备，我要
in this case and you're safe fullback
在这种情况下，你就可以安全地卫冕
method of fullback and then my fallback
后卫的方法，然后我的后备
method is going to call fullback and I'm
方法将调用后卫，我
going to do return new prop prop name
将要返回的新道具道具名称
and then I'll do system get property so
然后我将系统获取属性，以便
what I've done here is the method the
我在这里所做的是方法
method parameters are exactly the same
方法参数完全相同
the method return type is exactly the
方法的返回类型恰好是
same it's just the method name it's
一样，只是方法名称而已
different because they're in the same
不同，因为它们在同一个地方
class and when it fails this time after
类，当它这次失败后
500 seconds it's just doing a call this
500秒只是在打电话
one and the way you'll be able to tell
一种以及您将能够分辨的方式
is it'll start returning service a
它会开始返回服务吗
rather than service C so if i refresh
而不是服务C，所以如果我刷新
it says service I this is this this is
它说服务我这是这个
how you can tell but it has done the the
你怎么知道，但它已经完成了
full-back logic and if I went back and I
后卫的逻辑，如果我回去，我
changed the mode I could get it to
改变了我可以得到的模式
actually do the call again
真的再打一次电话
so that's the demo of company there is
这就是公司的演示
there are more things which I didn't
还有更多我没有的东西
have time to I don't have time to demo
有时间我没时间演示
there's support for the circuit breaker
有断路器的支持
patent this was I think demonstrated in
我认为这是在专利中展示的
the first talk this morning it basically
今天早上的第一次谈话基本上
allows you to do kind of self-healing so
可以让您进行自我修复
if you get a certain number of failures
如果您遇到一定数量的失败
it'll stop calling the downstream
它将停止呼叫下游
services it will automatically call your
服务会自动呼叫您
fallback method if you walk one set up
后备方法（如果您进行一次设置）
and then if the target service comes
然后如果目标服务来了
back up again it will kind of self heal
再次备份会自我修复
and start calling it once the target
然后一旦目标就开始调用它
services in a good good state
服务处于良好状态
there's also bulk heading so if you have
还有大量的标题，所以如果你有
if you have a downstream service that
如果您有下游服务，
has some kind of constraint on how many
对多少有某种限制
requests it can handle you can make sure
要求它可以处理您可以确保
you don't pass it so many requests it
您没有通过太多请求
can't it can't deal with sorry for
不能对不起
example it can only deal with ten
例如它只能处理十个
concurrent requests or you can say only
并发请求，或者您只能说
make ten concurrent requests at a time q
一次发出十个并发请求q
the other ones up until the next one is
其他的直到下一个是
is done now one of the questions that
现在完成的问题之一
quite often comes up is continuity of
经常出现的是连续性
service mesh like Sto and the answer is
像Sto这样的服务网格，答案是
sort of
有点
the reason I say sort of is because well
我说的原因是因为
the nice things about SDO is it gives
关于SDO的好处是
you the ability to add some fault
你有能力加一些毛病
tolerance behaviors at the network layer
网络层的容忍行为
and that means that you don't have to
这意味着您不必
code it all in your application the
将其全部编码在您的应用程序中
thing to be aware of when you do this is
执行此操作时要注意的是
it's a little bit less flexible because
灵活性较差，因为
it's only at the network layer so if you
它仅在网络层，所以如果您
want to do your kind of fault tolerance
想做你的容错
around a group of network interactions
围绕一组网络交互
like to rest calls or a restful database
喜欢休息电话或宁静的数据库
call then you can't because it would be
打电话，那么你不能，因为那会
applied to each outbound call the other
应用于对方的每个拨出电话
issue is that it's geo can't deal with
问题是它的地理位置无法处理
HTTP because HTT if you want HTS to be
HTTP，因为如果您希望HTS成为HTT
end-to-end encrypted so if you want to
端到端加密，因此如果您想
do use this do you need to have HTTP
用这个你需要HTTP吗
from your server say to the sto and then
从您的服务器说到sto，然后
the HTTP would go from there onwards but
HTTP将从那里开始，但是
you then you don't have kind of
你那么你就没有
end-to-end security so there are kind of
端到端的安全性
some limitations with this year there's
今年有一些限制
a kind of place for both of them so
对他们俩来说都是一个好地方
what's next
下一步是什么
Jovie eight that's kind of imminent I
Jovie八，我迫在眉睫
think
认为
in the next version of microphone file
在下一版本的麦克风文件中
I've just shown 1.3 there's a very
我刚刚展示了1.3，
active workgroup looking at how to bring
积极的工作组，研究如何带来
reactive program models to micro profile
反应程序模型到微轮廓
I have to say it kind of breaks my brain
我不得不说有点伤脑筋
the whole reactive thing but at the same
整个反应性事物，但同时
time I know enough to know that it's
我知道的时间足以知道
it's it's actually something that is
这是实际上是
really important and I'm trying to get
真的很重要，我正在努力
my head round there there's a discussion
我的头上有一个讨论
at the moment about data access because
目前有关数据访问的原因是
there's no statement on how to access
没有关于如何访问的声明
data it's kind of default to whether you
数据是您是否默认的一种
do it yourself will use JP a but JP is
自己做会使用JP a，但是JP是
not pass a micro profile there's a
没有通过微型个人资料
workgroup on how to improve the
有关如何改善
integration with this do because what
这样做，因为什么
you don't want to do is have an
你不想做的是
application annotation and an sto
应用程序注释和存储
captured for a retry because if they're
被捕获重试，因为如果
both through trying five times you're
通过尝试五次
going to be ending up re trying 25 times
将要重新尝试25次
in total at the network layer which is
总共在网络层
kind of crazy and of course we're always
有点疯狂，当然我们总是
updating the existing specs to make them
更新现有规格以使它们
better or based on feedback and one last
更好或基于反馈和最后
thing on deployment there was a question
部署方面有一个问题
from an earlier session about why you
从之前的会议中了解了为什么
would use a kind of a hollow jar
将使用一种空心罐
approach and there was an allusion to
的方法，有一个暗示
docker so I decided to keep this in my
码头工人，所以我决定将其保留在我的
deck so spring especially makes a big
甲板，所以春天特别大
thing about kind of uber jars or fat
关于超级罐子或脂肪的事情
jars depending on how you whether you
罐子取决于您是否
want to slightly negative or slightly
想要稍微消极或轻微
positive spin on them and it makes it
对他们积极的旋转，它使它
very easy for distributing your
非常容易分发您的
application and running it cuz you just
应用程序并运行它，因为你只是
do Java - jar but your that your kind of
做Java-jar，但是你那种
jar file is is quite big which means
jar文件很大，这意味着
every time you make a code change you're
每次更改代码时，
ending up pushing a rather large binary
最终推出了相当大的二进制文件
around so if you look at the pet clinic
因此，如果您看宠物诊所
spring break example it's about 40
春假的例子大约是40
megabytes the actual application is less
兆字节实际应用较少
than 400 kilobytes so if you're
超过400 KB，如果您
distributing a new bird jar around for
为附近分发一个新的鸟罐
that application
该应用程序
every time you deploy it's 40 megabytes
每次部署时40兆字节
being transferred around the network
通过网络传输
that's not a problem if you're deploying
如果您要部署，那不是问题
like once a week but if you're trying to
例如每周一次，但如果您尝试
do continuous delivery and every commit
持续交付和每次提交
is resulting in a poor into production
导致生产不良
you're probably doing
你可能正在做
hundreds of deploys in a day at which
每天有数百次部署
point the difference between 400 K and
指出400 K与
40 megabytes is significant and that's
40兆字节非常重要
where things like hollow jars come in
像空罐子这样的东西进来的地方
because what you can do is you can push
因为你能做的是你可以推动
you can have a specific layer for your
您可以为您的特定图层
essential kind of Application Platform
必不可少的应用平台
runtime server whatever you want to call
运行时服务器无论您要调用什么
it separate from the application layer
它与应用程序层分离
and because of the way docker works
并且由于码头工人的工作方式
although you think of a docker image as
尽管您认为Docker映像是
one thing it's actually a series of
一件事实际上是一系列的
layers with pointers to other layers so
具有指向其他图层的指针的图层
if you're pushing something it will only
如果你要推东西，那只会
send the layers that need to be sent so
发送需要发送的图层
in the left hand case if you've you've
如果是左手的话
changed is the application code is only
更改是仅应用程序代码
going to transfer the 400 kilobytes for
将要转移400 KB
the application which makes deployments
进行部署的应用程序
faster so I'm out of time so I'm just
更快，所以我没有时间，所以我只是
going to say this is the summary the
要说的是摘要
thing that I haven't mentioned already
我还没有提到的东西
in any way shape or form is if you want
无论如何，形状或形式都是
to know more if you go to this URL on
要了解更多信息，请访问以下网址：
the open Liberty website we have a whole
开放的自由网站，我们拥有一个整体
bunch of guides which go through every
一堆指南，通过每一个
single one of the technologies in in in
中的一项技术
micro profile there's even a couple of
微型个人资料甚至还有
interactive ones so if you only get kind
互动的，所以如果你只得到帮助
of code on your laptop you can kind of
在笔记本电脑上的代码，您可以
learn and understand some of the
学习和理解一些
patterns directly using in the web
模式直接在网络上使用
browser so thank you and I think I'm out
浏览器，谢谢，我想我已经走了
of time for questions so I'm sorry
有时间提问，对不起
you
您
[Applause]
[掌声]